Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives, 1982-2001 MSS.231
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XXI: Out on Wednesdays
  - Out on Wednesdays, 5/18/1994, ID: 231.1178 (Box 75, Media ID: 231.1178)
    Program content: 1. Al Sharpton, 2. The Pulse
  - [Container]--Out on Wednesdays, 5/18/1994 [Cassette]--[Unmarked], ID: 231.1179 (Box 75, Media ID: 231.1179)
    Program content: [Container]--Tom Duane, Teddy Kalidos, Suzanne Goldberg
  - Out on Wednesdays, 5/25/1994, ID: 231.1180 (Box 75, Media ID: 231.1180)
    Program content: 1. Jeff Richardson, 2. The Pulse
  - Out on Wednesdays, 7/6/1994, ID: 231.1181 (Box 76, Media ID: 231.1181)
    Program content: Rich Wandel, Jeremiah Newton
  - [1]--Out on Wednesdays, 7/20/1994 [2]--Out on Wednesdays, 7/13/1994, ID: 231.1182 (Box 76, Media ID: 231.1182)
    Program content: [2]--[Container]--Lesbian Gay and Bisexual Youth, Barbara Well Warren, Steve Weinstien with George [Clooney] [Cassette]--L G Bi Youth, Patricia Well Warren
  - Out on Wednesdays, 7/27/1994, ID: 231.1183 (Box 76, Media ID: 231.1183)
    Program content: Larry Kramer, The Pulse
  - Out on Wednesdays, 8/24/1994, ID: 231.1184 (Box 76, Media ID: 231.1184)
    Program content: Jerry Nadler and Tom Duane, The Pulse
  - [1]--Out on Wednesdays [2]--"Buffalo Slasher WGRZ No. 2", Undated; ID: 231.1185 (Box 76, Media ID: 231.1185)
    Program content: [1]--Andy Humm-Rich Wandel archivist for center, Interview-Jeff Richardson-Exec. Dir. GMH[C]
- Series XXII: Political Conventions
  Titles and program content have been transcribed from original container annotations. These tapes have not been viewed by an archivist.
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 1, Platform Meeting --No. 3 Beefcake, also Democratic Platform Committee, Overview-Virginia Apuzzo, Geraldine Ferrara, June 11, 1984; 2013; 231.1306 (Box 86, U-matic 231.1306)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 2, Platform Committee, Washington --Dem. Platform Committee-WDC No. 4, June 12, 1984; 231.1307 (Box 86, U-matic 231.1307)
    Interview with Bill Kraus-California, Terry Anderson-Vermont
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 3, Platform Committee, Dem. National Caucus-WDC No. 5, June 12, 1984; 231.1308 (Box 86, U-matic 231.1308)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 4, Democratic Platform Committee WDC, 2013; 231.1309 (Box 86, U-matic 231.1309)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 6 --Virginia Apuzzo No. 10; Parade Tape 1, ID: 231.1310 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1310)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 7, Gay Parade Tape No. 2, ID: 231.1311 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1311)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 8, Gay Parade Tape No. 3, ID: 231.1312 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1312)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 9, Gay Parade Tape No. 4, ID: 231.1313 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1313)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 10, NALGDC (A), [1]--Gay/Lesbian Delegate Conference SF No. 3, 7/13/1984 [2]--Democratic Platform Conference No. 7, July 13, 1984; ID: 231.1314 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1314)
    Program content: Viginia Apuzzo before delegation
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 11, NALGDC (B), Gay/Lesbian Delegate Conference SF First Day No. 4, July 13, 1984; ID: 231.1315 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1315)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 12, NALGDC (C), [1]--National Association of Lesbian/Gay Democratic Clubs SF Second Day No. 1 [2]--National Association of Lesbian/Gay Democratic Clubs 1st Day, July 14, 1984; ID: 231.1316 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1316)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 13, NALGDC Day 2, National Association of Lesbian/Gay Democratic Clubs Second Day Tape No. 2, ID: 231.1317 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1317)
    Program content: Minnesota Delegate
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 14, NAGLDC Day 2 SF, July 14, 1984; ID: 231.1318 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1318)
    Program content: Judith Goldsmith
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 15, NAGLDC Day 2 SF, July 14, 1984; ID: 231.1319 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1319)
    Program content: [Container]--Election of Officers, Gay and Lesbian Caucus, Peter Vogel [Cassette]--Delegate Caucus Opening-Bill Krauss
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 16, Lesbian and Gay Caucus Day 2, July 14, 1984; ID: 231.1320 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1320)
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 17, Lesbian and Gay Caucus Day 2, July 14, 1984; ID: 231.1321 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1321)
    Program content: End of Day, Democratic Caucus Platform Committee SF, Interview Delegate of Maine-Murder, Edith E. 1st Tape
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 18, Convention (A) Third Day, July 16, 1984; ID: 231.1322 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1322)
    Program content: Moscone Center, Delegate interviews, Cuomo Speech, NGTF (WDC)-Jeff Lovi interview
  - [1]--Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 20, Convention (C) Fourth Day [2]--Democratic Convention No. 19, July 17, 1984; ID: 231.1323 (Box 86, U-matic ID: 231.1323)
    Program content: Delegate interview, Jesse Jackson speech, Gay/lesbian [Anniversaries] by Jackson
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 21, Convention (D) Fifth Day, ID: 231.1324 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1324)
    Program content: Interviews, Gov. Maine, [Vogol] etc.
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 22, Convention (E) Fifth Day, ID: 231.1325 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1325)
    Program content: Mayor Koch, Delegate interview
  - [1]--Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 24, Convention (G) Sixth Day [2]--Judith Sasine, Resume Tape, FA III 1982, ID: 231.1326 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1326)
    Program content: Glide Church, Intro, Judy Goldsmith
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 1, August 16, 1984; ID: 231.1327 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1327)
    Program content: Dallas-Phyllis Diller interview, Dallas-Majestic Theatre, "Eyes of Texas," 1st Pamela Stanley
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 2, Texas Command Performance, ID: 231.1328 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1328)
    Program content: Pamala Stanley, Texas Freedom Award for Don Baker
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 3, Texas Command Performance, ID: 231.1329 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1329)
    Program content: Don Baker Speech, Texas Freedom Awards, Entertainment-Bob Bishop Singer, Ted Weisser Sextet
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 4, Texas Command Performance, ID: 231.1330 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1330)
    Program content: 1. Bob Bishop, 2. Phyllis Diller, NGTF Ads
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 5, Texas Command Performance, ID: 231.1331 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1331)
    Program content: Phyllis Diller Tape No. 4
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 6, Texas Command Performance-Last, ID: 231.1332 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1332)
    Program content: 1. Phyllis Diller-Last, Keeping America Safe for Human Rights, A-Susan Jester, B-Marshall Mason
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 7, Keeping America Safe for Human Rights No. 2, ID: 231.1333 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1333)
    Program content: 1. Marshall Mason part 2, 2. Larry Bush, 3. John Eaton
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 8, Keeping America Safe for Human Rights-Final, ID: 231.1334 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1334)
    Program content: Mirium Binschalom-Sergeant in Army, Acon Convention, Bruce Decker, Concerned Americans for Individual Rights, City Lights-Dallas
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 9, First Convention, ID: 231.1335 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1335)
    Program content: Lann Ashley, Dennella Jackson, Phil Gramm, Janet Dye, Marilyn Payne
  - [1]--Republican National Convention 1984 No. 11 [2]--Blue Boy Contest, ID: 231.1336 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1336)
    Program content: Bill Robinson, Mirium Hellwright, Norma Vargus; Year drawn from "GCN Archives Inventory" Binder, see Series Box [Old No. 239] Folder
    Duration: 21 minutes
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 12, ID: 231.1337 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1337)
    Program content: Virgin Island Delegate, "Maureen Reagan," Protect at Minage, Robert Bacci, Concerned Republican for Individual Rights, Pastor Don Eastman, MCC Church
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 13, Minage Interviews, ID: 231.1338 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1338)
    Program content: 1. Ted Page, 2. Bill Filante, 3. Bill Radcliffe
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 14, ID: 231.1339 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1339)
    Program content: 1. Eleonar Rice, 2. Dallas Skyline and Long Horn cattle, Joe Hughes-Colorado, Kirpatrick-Speech
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 15, Minage, ID: 231.1340 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1340)
    Program content: Phyllis Johnson, Rev. Prevo-Alaska, Elephants, Seal, Band, Rev. Prevo, First Lady
  - [1]--Republican National Convention 1984 No. 16, Mike Richards on AIDS [2]--Metroguide, 4/24/1983, 1983-1984; ID: 231.1341 (Box 87, U-matic ID: 231.1341)
    Program content: [1]--15:24-Ronald Reagan accept [your] nomination
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 17, First Lady, ID: 231.1342 (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1342)
    Program content: Reagan Nomination, 1st part of interviews, Larry Fry
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 18, ID: 231.1343 (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1343)
    Program content: Bill Nelson-DGA President, Toni Stuart-CAIR-Concerned Americans for Individual Rights-Local organizer
  - Republican National Convention 1984 No. 20, ID: 231.1344 (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1344)
    Program content: 1. Martin Trego, 2. Melody Alexander, 3. Mike Richards
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 19, [1]--Third Day [2]--Fourth Day, ID: 231.1345 (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1345)
    Program content: [1]--Crowd shots into Moscon center [2]--Delegate interviews
  - Democratic National Convention 1984 No. 23, Convention (F) [1]--Fifth Day [2]--Sixth Day, ID: 231.1346 (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1346)
    Program content: [1]--Gay Caucus march [2]--Gay Caucus Press Conference
  - Conventions '88 Opening Elements, July 11, 1988; ID: 231.1347 (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1347)
  - Conventions '88, Demonstration Protest No. 1, July 17, 1988; ID: 231.1348A (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1348A)
  - Conventions '88, No. 2, July 17, 1988; ID: 231.1349A (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1349A)
    Program content: [Protester], Perry Watkins, Ted Weiss, Joe Tom Easlay, Ray Hill, Martin Hiraga
  - Conventions '88, BBQ Dinner No. 1, July 17, 1988; ID: 231.1350A (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1350A)
    Program content: Barney Frank
  - Conventions '88, BBQ Dinner No. 2, July 17, 1988; ID: 231.1351A (Box 88, Media ID: 231.1351A)
    Program content: Camera-Lou, Vivian and Barney Frank
  - Conventions '88, Delegates Interviews No. 1, July 17, 1988; ID: 231.1352A (Box 88, Media ID: 231.1352A)
    Program content: Camera-Harry, Family Issues
  - Conventions '88, On the Floor P.M. No. 1, July 18, 1988; ID: 231.1353A (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1353A)
    Program content: Discrimination, Brian
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen On the Floor No. 1, July 18, 1988; ID: 231.1354A (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1354A)
    Program content: Interviews on Family Caucus, 7 interviews on Family issues, Gay nephew, sharing life together (what is family?), Pat Paulsen, Terry Lewis (VJ. Gay Dem)
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen No. 2, July 18, 1988; ID: 231.1355A (Box 88, Media ID: 231.1355A)
    Program content: Big Interview Key Person, Jim Fagelson-Gay Parent Group-Family, Carole Migden-openly lesbian head of San Francisco Dem Party elected to Dem. National Comm. '88 Platform Comm., at Gay Caucus
  - Conventions '88, [1]--Intro and Rap Up, July 18, 1988 [2]--Intros to Tuesdays Events from Studio, July 19, 1988, July 18-19, 1988; ID: 231.1356 (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1356)
  - Conventions '88, Jeff and Olivia On Floor A.M. No. 1 of 1, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1357A (Box 88, Media ID: 231.1357A)
    Program content: Melba Moore interview, Tim Becker-del Nebraska, [Marjarie] Brush
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Mayor's Office No. 1, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1358A (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1358A)
    Program content: Mayor's Office, Testimony by ACT-UP protestors hit by cops in Kiss-in, Interview with 3 street people, Interview with born agains
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Mayor's Office No. 2, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1359A (Box 88, U-matic ID: 231.1359A)
    Program content: Song-We are Lesbian and Gay People, Testimony-ACT-UP in office
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-A.M. No. 2, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1360A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1360A)
    Program content: Interviews-delegates Herb Schultz and Beth Marschak regarding discrimination, Vic Basile-long interview on violence, descrimination, national gay leaders, AIDS, and what's happening here.
  - Conventions '88, [1]--Kathleen-A.M. No. 4, July 19, 1988 [2]--Gay Caucus No. 4, July 21,1988, July 19, 1988, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1361A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1361A)
    Program content: [Denny] Watkins after nominated for V. Pres., Andy and Jeff interview, Intros to Tuesday 7/19/1988
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-On the Floor P.M. No. 6, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1362A (Box 89, Media ID: 231.1362A)
    Program content: Melba Moore singing, two good interviews on AIDS, Good shot of gay male on floor holding a large 'Silence=Death' Pink Triangle, Lots of ambient hoop-la at J. Jackson's speech
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor No. 2, 7/19/1988, ID: 231.1363A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1363A)
    Program content: AIDS, John McLaughlin, Morgen Fairchild, Rob Lowe, Ben Hooks (NAACP)
  - Conventions '88, Atlanta Democratic National Convention No. 2, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1364A (Box 89, Media ID: 231.1364A)
    Program content: Day 2
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 1, July 20, 1988; ID: 231.1365A (Box 89, Media ID: 231.1365A)
    Program content: Andrew Young Press Conference, ACT-UP Interviews, Martin Luther King II CTR AIDS interview, interviews with tourists
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 2, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1366A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1366A)
    Program content: Interviews at Martin Luther King etc, a lot of panning and fill, close up of Coretta Scott King, Kids and AIDS education
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Convention Center Night No. 1, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1367A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1367A)
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Convention Center No. 2, July 20, 1988; ID: 231.1368A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1368A)
  - Conventions '88, Phil-Omni Perimeter No. 1, July 20, 1988; ID: 231.1369A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1369A)
    Program content: Monihan/Bradley/etc, Paul Simon
  - Conventions '88, Phil-Omni No. 2, July 20, 1988; ID: 231.1370A (Box 89, Media ID: 231.1370A)
    Program content: Al Gore (good), McGovern, Art Agnos
  - Conventions '88, Piggy and Olivia-Convention Floor No. 1, July 20, 1988; ID: 231.1371A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1371A)
  - Conventions '88, Piggy and Olivia-Convention Floor No. 2, July 20, 1988; ID: 231.1372A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1372A)
    Program content: Jeff, camera person, Olivia N., Interviewer, Pigg Team
  - Conventions '88, Piggy and Olivia-Atlanta Gay Center, July 20, 1988; ID: 231.1373A (Box 89, Media ID: 231.1373A)
    Program content: Richard Swanson, Bill Gripp
  - Conventions '88, Piggy-Atlanta Gay Center, July 20, 1988; ID: 231.1374A (Box 89, Media ID: 231.1374A)
    Program content: PWA interview-Steve Warner
  - Conventions '88, Piggs and Olivia closing No. 3, July 20, 1988; ID: 231.1375A (Box 89, Media ID: 231.1375A)
  - Conventions '88, [Atlanta Democratic National Convention] No. 3, 1988; ID: 231.1376A (Box 89, Media ID: 231.1376A)
    Program content: AIDS
  - Conventions '88, Intros and Rap-ups in Studio Wednesday, July 20, 1988; ID: 231.1377A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1377A)
  - Conventions '88, Floor Crew 1 P.M. No. 1, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1378A (Box 89, U-matic ID: 231.1378A)
    Program content: Olivia Comment, Paul Simon, Al Gore, Claude Pepper
  - Conventions '88, Floor Crew 1 P.M. No. 3, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1379A (Box 90, U-matic ID: 231.1379A)
    Program content: Good footage of very end of Dukakis speech and parade of people to podium plus crowd shots
  - Conventions '88, Floor Crew 1 P.M. No. 5, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1380 (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1380)
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-Floor Crew 2 P.M. No. 1, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1381A (Box 90, U-matic ID: 231.1381A)
    Program content: John Seagliotli WBA, NJ Sen. Frank Lautenberg, Ark. Gov. Bill Clinton, Linda Lavin, NY Newsday's Sydney Schanberg, Dick Gerhardt, Paul Simon, Stanley Hill-Labor, Why Vote Democratic and Linda Lavin, [Geohead]-Simon
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-Floor Crew 2 P.M. No. 3, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1382A (Box 90, U-matic ID: 231.1382A)
    Program content: End of Dukakis speech, Andy stand-up on floor at end, Minnesota delegate reactions, Crowd/Balloons, Personal messages, Rex Wockner-gay journalist
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-Floor Crew 2 P.M. No. 4, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1383A (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1383A)
    Program content: Ed Asner/Richard Mazur, Bill Nichov, David Dinkins, Allen Roskoff, Willie Brown (CA), Andy Kopkind, People from AZ and WI
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-Floor Crew 2 P.M. No. 5, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1384A (Box 90, U-matic ID: 231.1384A)
    Program content: Reactions to Dukakis speech, A yuppie, Jim Wright House Speaker, Sen. Patrick Leahy, Ann Richards, Tom Foley House Maj. Leader, Jason Worth, Miguel Gomez
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-Floor Crew 2 P.M. No. 7, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1385A (Box 90, U-matic ID: 231.1385A)
    Program content: Dukakis Speech, Robert Farrell-L.A. City Council, Randy Sullivan-gay del. (OR), Olympia Dukakis, Introduction of Mike Dukakis, Dukakis at Podium
  - Conventions '88, Floor Crew 1 P.M. No. 2, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1386A (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1386A)
    Program content: Willie Brown, Barbara Jordan, Judd Nelson, Bentsen speech, AIDS-Dukakis speech
  - Conventions '88, Phil and Kate, Gay Caucus No. 2, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1387 (Box 90, U-matic ID: 231.1387)
  - Conventions '88, Phil and Kate, Gay Caucus No. 3, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1388A (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1388A)
    Program content: Studio, Phil intro to Gay Caucus and KRM, Crew commentaries
  - Conventions '88, Phil and Kate, Gay Caucus No. 4, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1389 (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1389)
  - Conventions '88, Phil and Kate, Gay Caucus No. 5, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1390 (Box 90, U-matic ID: 231.1390)
  - Conventions '88, Phil, WCC Kiss-in, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1391 (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1391)
    Program content: ACT-UP demonstration
  - Conventions '88, Andy Humm No. 1, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1392A (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1392A)
    Program content: Studio, Intros-Opens-Closes, Press interviews, Andy/Vivian
  - Conventions '88, Andy Humm No. 2, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1393A (Box 90, U-matic ID: 231.1393A)
    Program content: Taped in Studio, Intros and commentaries
  - Conventions '88, Atlanta Democratic National Convention No. 4, July 21, 1988; ID: 231.1394A (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1394A)
  - Conventions '88, ACT UP Demonstration outside convention No. 3, July 17, 1988; ID: 231.1395A (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1395A)
    Program content: Skinheads, Bob Kunst
  - Conventions '88, Andy Humm Exteriors/Introductions, July 17, 1988; ID: 231.1396A (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1396A)
    Program content: Convention centre interior and exterior, Andy overvoice and intro, interviews at lesbian party
  - Conventions '88, Introductions and Wrap ups, July 18, 1988; ID: 231.1397 (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1397)
    Program content: Monday studio
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen No. 1, July 18, 1988; ID: 231.1398A (Box 90, Media ID: 231.1398A)
    Program content: General gay voice action center, Jeff Levin, Vic Bassile
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-On the Floor P.M. No. 2, July 18, 1988; ID: 231.1399A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1399A)
    Program content: Ann Richards (Speech), Mike Farrell actor (discrimination), Terry Anderson, New Jersey, New York signs
  - Conventions '88, Atlanta Democratic National Convention No. 1, July 18, 1988; ID: 231.1400A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1400A)
    Program content: Day One, Demonstrations
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-A.M. No. 1, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1401A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1401A)
    Program content: Gay press conference, Karen Clark, Perry [Atkins], Dale McCormick, gay discrimination
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-A.M. No. 3, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1402A (Box 91, U-matic ID: 231.1402A)
    Program content: Vic Basile cont., 1 guest, Eleanor Smeal-former pres. NOW, establishing shot, important gay caucus to nominate v. pres., interviews after P. Watkins nominated for vice-pres., Pat Worman, F. Butner
  - Conventions '88, Kathleen-On the Floor P.M. No. 5, July 19, 1988; ID: 231.1403A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1403A)
    Program content: Albert Gore, several good interviews, Mondale, AIDS
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 1, August 13, 1988; ID: 231.1404A (Box 91, U-matic ID: 231.1404A)
    Program content: AIDS Candlelight, Armstrong Park
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 2, August 13, 1988; ID: 231.1405A (Box 91, U-matic ID: 231.1405A)
    Program content: AIDS Candlelight
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 3, August 13, 1988; ID: 231.1406A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1406A)
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 4, August 13, 1988; ID: 231.1407A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1407A)
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 5, August 13, 1988; ID: 231.1408A (Box 91, U-matic ID: 231.1408A)
    Program content: Bourbon St.
  - Conventions '88, Allen/Negron NOW Rally, No. 1, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1409A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1409A)
  - Conventions '88, Armstrong Park Care Fest, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1410A (Box 91, U-matic ID: 231.1410A)
    Program content: Camera-Parker, Corres. O/Allen
  - Conventions '88, ACT UP Arrestees from Country Club No. 1, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1411A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1411A)
  - Conventions '88, Harry No. 1, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1412A (Box 91, U-matic ID: 231.1412A)
    Program content: Rally at Kiss-in St. Louis Cathedral
  - Conventions '88, Young Republicans No. 2, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1413A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1413A)
    Program content: Camera-Parker, Corres. O. Negron, NOW Rally
  - Conventions '88, ACT UP Reagan, August 14, 1988; ID: 231.1414A (Box 91, U-matic ID: 231.1414A)
    Program content: New Orleans Convention Center, ACT-UP protest of Reagan speech, Footage of outside and inside protests, Interview with Adam Hassuk of ACT-UP describing what happened inside, Chyron-"Courtesy of Testing the Limits"
  - Conventions '88, Gay Republican Party No. 1, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1415A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1415A)
    Program content: At the mint
  - Conventions '88, Gay Republican Party No. 2, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1416A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1416A)
  - Conventions '88, Allen AIDS delegates, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1417A (Box 91, U-matic ID: 231.1417A)
    Program content: Camera-Parker, PA-Tad
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor Crew 1 No. 1, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1418A (Box 91, Media ID: 231.1418A)
    Program content: Family, (Ed and Olivia), Gay Vote
  - Conventions '88, Steve-Floor Crew 1 No. 2, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1419A (Box 92, U-matic ID: 231.1419A)
    Program content: Ed-O, Camera-Steve, N/G
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Floor Crew 2 No. 1, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1420A (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1420A)
    Program content: (Andy and Allen), Family, Vote
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Floor Crew 2 No. 2, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1421A (Box 92, U-matic ID: 231.1421A)
    Program content: (Andy and Allen), Family Issues, Reagan reaction, 10:40 No civil rights
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Floor Crew 2 No. 3, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1422A (Box 92, U-matic ID: 231.1422A)
    Program content: End Mom's demonstration, Intro/outro demo, Rep. reactions, Gay Vote
  - Conventions '88, Harry-Floor Crew 2 No. 4, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.1423A (Box 92, Media ID: 231.1423A)
    Program content: Wrap ups/intros, Mon. Show